Hello friends, my name is Pramod Saraswat
and I have been working in this financial industry for the last 17 years. With your
love, I have won many awards.
Top of the Industry, be it
your Code Club, ABS,
Aditya Birla & Key Club, MFD
Club, or Adar Health Insurance Products.
We
provide our services to almost 2000 clients today.
Friends, today I am among you with
a special product in which generally
our customers talk to us, Pramod,
we need a guaranteed income for a long time
and that too we do not want to wait for a very long time,
either from next month
or next year or I will start getting it after some time.
We usually
recommend them to other such classes or other instruments
because we do not have all these products on time.
Today,
I have brought to you a product
that you will be surprised to hear and you will
definitely think about this product. So yes
friends, this product is from Aditya
Birla Sun Life Insurance Company, whose
plan is named Nishtha.  Aayu ji
is the fixed Ayushman of Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Company. In this plan,
you will have the option to spend 6 years
on PM only, you will have the option to spend 8 years
on PM only, you will have the option to
spend 10 years on PM only and 12 years on PM only.
Similarly, you have the option of
Doberman income or
immediate income in this, so today I will
talk as an example, suppose you spend Rs 600000 on PM for the next 10
years and start earning from the next year itself,
then you
get income in it,
that too for the next 40 years, similarly at the
end of 40 years you also get Rs 84 lakh tax free
and guaranteed and along with that
you get risk cover of 60% loss, so
friends, we have invested Rs 7 lakh in total in a span of 10 years
and we get to get both
income plus majority in an instrument of Rs 60 lakh, Rs
7640000.  Yes friends, this
is totally guaranteed and tax free and
along with this, insurance is an additional feature
which you get. In this, there is another
option of Doberman, that is, option
B. Let me talk as an example.
Suppose I have made any plan that I am earning ₹6
lakh every year, but I default on income for one
year, that is,
I start taking income from the second year, then
my income in it increases, that is, it
increases, so that income becomes
Rs. 600, which I will get under the first option A.
Plus, in this also you will get Rs. 84 at the end of 40 years, so that
means by combining both the income plus majority, you get Rs. 10
crore 83 lakh 68000 400. So, in this
also you are totally tax free and guaranteed,
as I am talking about, friends,
as you must have seen that the interest rate was
decreasing a lot in the past and many of our
customers had the same question, friend, according to which the
interest rate is very low.  It is happening
but we are
not getting security for the long term, see
how much money we will earn from the market or not
and you have the option to take it after 1 year or
even after one year of depreciation,
for more information you
can contact us on the number given below
or you can connect 121 by filling the form,
friends my vision is to deliver
this product to 200 families at their doorstep within the next 1 year
and you all will support me in this mission
and I want that maximum number of people should
watch this video live,
subscribe and forward this to your near and dear ones whom
you love,
thank you